Hello, you. Let me tell you a story.

A few months ago I went through a heartbreak. While I was going through the usual sad and crying stages of heartbreak, my cousin came to me and convinced me to learn to code. After doing some research on my own I sat in front of my computer to learn to code and haven't got up since then.

After starting to build my own website I was amazed how coding invoked my creative side and interest in creating and building something. And it quickly became one thing that keep me up all night, without coffee.

Since I learned how much I could do with coding, I have done my best to make coding my daily routine. I enrolled in Bloc Online Bootcamp and always search for ideas for my articles and challenge myself with learning a new thing every day. So keeping myself busy with new challenges I was back to normal from the hearbreak.

With my new knowledge of coding, plus previous work experiences I believe I can be good value to any company and deliver a good work.

Thank you for taking the time to read my story.

## **Objective and Education**

	Interested in a new co	اممد مصمدنيدمين	مام منابع منام	
Objective	Interested in a new e	xperience and	continuing ae	velopment of

programming skills and communication.

**Education** Bloc Online Bootcamp

2016

Front End Developer

**Elgin Community College** 

*Chicago, Illinois 2011-2013*Graphic Web Design

A + Nail School

Chicago, Illinois 2010-2011

Nail Technician

**Manhattan High School** 

Manhattan, Kansas 2005-2006

**MUS High School** 

Ulaanbaatar Mongolia 2004

**Technical Skills** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Adobe Photoshop and Adobe

Illustrator

### **Work Experience**

### **Owner / Manager**

#### **Red 6 Nails**

April 2013 - May 2016

After many years of experience in beauty

industry, me and my 2 sisters opened the door for our own beauty salon in 2013. Our goal was to provide high-quality service a sanitary environment that everyone can relax. With the responsibility as owner and manager, I expanded my experience in excellent customer service, handling appointments, training new employees, managing

appointments, training new employees, managing inventory and providing a workable environment for our employees.

Red 6 Nails client reviews...

"Love this hidden gem! The gold standard in nail care."

- Georgetta E.

"I have been coming here for a little over a year and LOVE this place. They just went through a remodel, and the place looks amazing. Nice environment, friendly people, and most

importantly they do and excellent pedicure and manicure, as well as a great job keeping my eyebrows in check! They have some skills in nail art!"

- Mary L.

### **Work Experience** Continued

#### **Nail technician**

#### **Nail Bliss**

March 2012 - March 2013

### **Blooming Nails**

February 2010 - February 2012

With my new nail technician license in hand and with huge knowledge in mind I quickly entered the work field and started to build my own clientele by providing an excellent service and caring for each client with special care for their individual needs.

#### Server

### Naomi Sushi

*April 2006 - February 2010* 

My first job as a server I really believe it shaped me to be a good employee. By working in a very popular restaurant I earned an ability to work in a fast-paced environment, multitasking and being responsible for customers satisfaction. Soon I started to mentor and train new servers with knowledge of restaurant system and procedures.

## **Contact Information**

**Phone** 773.698.4554

**Email** jagamongol@gmail.com

**URL** jagamongol.com